#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/edzel-mutas-326b73129 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

2D Animation Adobe After Effects Adobe Photoshop

### Certifications

Microsoft Office Specialist: Word Associate (Office 2019)

Microsoft Office Specialist: Associate (Office 2019)

Microsoft Office Specialist: Excel Associate (Office 2019)

Microsoft Excel (Office 2016)

Microsoft Office Specialist: PowerPoint Associate (Office 2019)

# **Edzel Mutas**

Course Instructor at Father Saturnino Urios University Butuan, Caraga, Philippines

## Summary

I am a Motion Graphic artist and video editor, specializing in Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro. I've been creating videos since 2012, working as a freelancer to deliver visually compelling content. In addition to freelancing, I teach at Father Saturnino Urios University, where I handle major subjects like 2D Animation, 3D Animation, 3D Modelling, 3D Texturing, and Graphics and Design.

## Experience

Father Saturnino Urios University 10 years 7 months

Instructor

June 2014 - Present (10 years 7 months)

Course Instructor

June 2014 - Present (10 years 7 months)

Butuan, Caraga, Philippines

### Education

Ateneo de Naga University

Master of Computer Graphics and Animation, Digital Arts, Animation, Production · (June 2017 - March 2020)